my name is chase the founder of Blok Blok Studio i can tell
you all the case studies in
the world for our business but if you don't know me as a
person it doesn't even matter
so i'm gonna introduce myself my name is chase i'm from san
diego california i grew up a lot
in the u.s ended up on the east coast i joined the marine
corps i was in for five years got out
moved up to new york city to parsons school of design got my
degree and a bachelor's of
fine arts and design and technology after that founded my
agency Blok Blok Studio in june of
2024 then i moved out to berlin germany about a year later
from there we've just been scaling the
business it's been growing everything is ramping up we have a
team of four people now i got my
creative director in virginia my marketing strategist out in
la and my full stack dev here in berlin
germany it's been an amazing ride and we're here every single
day kicking it would love to work with
you below you're going to see a bunch of case studies you're
going to see four examples of the work we've
done go through it check it out if you've got questions let
me know on instagram or email
whatever works best for you below that we got a lead form
just put all your information in it comes
straight to me i'll check it out we'll hop on a call we'll
see if it works if it works great if not
it is what it is but i'm really looking forward to meeting
you and you guys have a great day talk to you
See you later.